ISAAC FIUZA



fiuzaisaac@hotmail.com



(801)979-4813



linkedin.com/in/isaac-fiuza-2b9104100

https://github.com/ifiuza?tab=repositories

Summary

SUMMARY

Configuration Specialist / Web Developer / Technical Support / Data Analyst

Educated with an A.S. in Computer Science. Certificate from the University of Utah - Full Stack Web Developer. Strengths in communication, problem

isolation, and solution, time management.

Experience



Configuration Specialist

InComm Payments

Jan 2022 - May 2023 (1 year 5 months)

- Follow documented configuration steps, use appropriate tools to implement high volume configurations routinely.
- Use problem solving skills, and the ability to recognize issues within InComm platforms and engage System Specialists for resolution
- Provide Level 3 Support to troubleshoot production problems and implement necessary configuration fixes
- Provide technical consulting to resolve configuration challenges of partners, processors and merchants during project implementations.
- Become a subject matter expert to business analysis and guide development teams on how to design and implement new solutions that can be easily configured.

LaunchIT · Splunk · ServiceNow · Gift Cards · Collaboration · Data Analysis - Logs: HTML-JavaScript-Java · Project Management · Microsoft SQL Server · Communication · Time Management

Product Support Analyst

InComm Payments

Jan 2021 - Jan 2022 (1 year 1 month)

responsible for supporting day-to-day business operations by providing second-level technical support.

- Troubleshooting / Tickets via ServiceNow
- Answer inbound telephone calls, e-mail enquiries from corporate clients, consumers and selling partners.
- Resolve inbound tickets assigned to the FLOS team. Resolve issues related to InComm Gifting & Financial card programs. (Gaming cards, phone cards, gift cards, pay as you go wireless products, health cards and financial products (gift & reloadable Visa, Amex, MasterCard). General functions include:
- Open/resolve/escalate/close tickets.
- Administrative tasks (partner account updates, provide activity reports).
- Troubleshoot store-based terminal issues. Diagnose connectivity issues.
- Troubleshoot point-of-sale-activation issues. Assist merchants when they have issues with

their POS terminals, Account updates, card orders, invoicing.

 Opening tickets to the appropriate technical teams when required.
Keep clients appraised on resolution progress.

Technical Support Specialist

Morgan Stanley

Jan 2020 - Dec 2020 (1 year)

Remote access issues

• Troubleshooting via ServiceNow: printers, apps, login issues and others.

🔤 Technical Support Specialist

BioFire Diagnostics, LLC

Jan 2019 - Dec 2019 (1 year)

Successfully Upgraded and continue to upgrade company's assets to Windows 10 to meet January deadline • Follow provided documentation to provision new Windows 10 Computers • Follow provided documentation to perform in place upgrades from Windows 7 to Windows 10 • Utilize provided checklists

to ensure computer setup accuracy • Troubleshooting of failed in place upgrades Schedule and Dispatch - Customer Service and Tech Support 2017 - 2018 Dell EMC Salt Lake City, UT

• English, Spanish and Portuguese Customer Service • Provided Excellent Support for Customers and Engineers of Dell EMC • Escalations as Needed •, Scheduling Technicians to Resolve Issues to end users

Finance Manager

Fiuza Motors LLC

Jan 2007 - Jan 2018 (11 years 1 month)

Smart purchased dealership inventory through online auctions that generated the company great profit

• Maintained inventory records with Microsoft Excel • Extensive reporting/Data Entry Finance Manager

Maintained records for dealership inventory, car sales (averaging 60 sales per month), and customers with DealerTrack software

Education



University of Utah

Bootcamp Certificate, Full Stack Web Development

2018 - 2019

Bootcamp Certificate: University of Utah, Salt Lake City, UT

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

Salt Lake Community College

Associate of Science, CS; Computer Science and Information Systems 2013-2015

Google (Coursera)

Data Analyst Course

Skills Learned: Sheets – BigQuery(SQL) - Tableau – R Programing Language

2023-2024